

NGUYEN VAN A

MARKETING MANAGER

Male

May 19, 1992

♥ Hanoi, Vietnam

fb.com/quynhtom design

Take advantages of sales skills & experience and ucimus, qui blanditiis praesentium vo of market to become a professional Sales Staff and bring a lot value to Customers. From that, I will contribute to development of CVPRO Company.

EDUCATION



FOREIGN TRADE UNIVERSITY

major. or desire administration

mm Sep 2007 - Present

FOREIGN TRADE UNIVERSITY

major. corporate administration

mm Sep 2007 - Present

EXPERIENCE



Sep 2007 - Present

CVPRO JSC

Sale Executive

Main responsibilities:

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult ska and answer customers' queries via phone and email.
- Assist to control goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

Recognition and Gains:

- Advertising products of the Company to customers effectively: contribute to a 20% increase in the number of customers within one month of working

Sep 2007 - Present

CVPRO JSC

Sale Executive

Main responsibilities:

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult products and answer customers' queries via phone and
- Assist to g the 15th century and others the 20th. Typesetter selecting ty goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

Recognition and Gains:

- Advertising products of the Company to customers effectively: contribute

ACTIVITIES



Sep 2003 - 2007

CVPRO JSC

Sale Executive

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult products and answer r incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Ut enim ad minim veniam, quis no' queries via phone and email.
- Assist to control goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

CERTIFICATIONS



TOEIC Certificate With Score 800 Issued By CVPRO 2004

HONORS & AWARDS



TOEIC Certificate With Score 800 Issued By CVPRO

2013 - 2014

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION



- Organize monthly events, network with US alumni
- Share how to hunt scholarships and US student's life experiences to all students who have received offers from US ons by H. Rac

REFERENCES



NGUYEN VAN BINH

director of cvpro jsc

SKILLS



Words Photoshop

Excel English

Power Point Japanese

INTERESTS



- Organize monthly events, network with US alumni
- Share how to hunt cách thêm các yếu tố hài hước, các từ ngẫu nhiên có and US student's life experiences to all students who have received offers from US universities